clareflorist.co.uk 2017-09-25

# Privacy Policy Terms | Clare Florist Privacy Information

At Clare Florist honesty is important to us and we are committed to protecting your privacy while shopping online. We will use the information that you provide us lawfully in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. 

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

The type of information we will collect about you includes: 

-Name   
-Address   
-Phone number   
-Email address   
-Credit/Debit Card Details when processing payment 

This information is collected when you create an account with us or when you place an order for flowers online or when you order over the telephon with us. 

### What We Do With This Information 

We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and second, to provide you with the best possible service. 

We will not e-mail you in the future unless we have your consent. We do not and will not share your e-mail address, personal information or purchase information with other traders unless you agree. 

In these circumstances we will always give you the option to opt out of receiving information from Clare Florist in our weekly emails. If you would rather not receive this information you can unsubscribe from the link on the email or contact us to be removed from our mailing list. 

The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. If you find any inaccuracies we will change it. 

### Security   

We take online security seriously and use a secure sockets layer (SSL) certificate to encrypt data transmissions on our website during the checkout process. We make sure that all of our payment processing pages are kept up to date and extremely secure for your own peace of mind. 

Your personal details will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the applicable laws of Scotland, England and Wales. 

### How We Use Cookies  

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. 

A cookie does not give us any access to your computer or sends over any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies when you visit our site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, and you can modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer. However this may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

Our website also uses Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of our website, but will not store, save or collect personal information about you. You can read Google's privacy policy [**here** ](http://www.google.com/privacy.html "Privacy Policy") for further information. 

### Links to other websites

On our website we may link to other websites of similiar interests. Please note that we do not have any control over that other website, and whilst we do our best to only link to popular and trusted pages, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

### More Information   

If you need any assistance please email [support@clareflorist.co.uk](mailto:support@clareflorist.co.uk)
